alltimefavorites.com 2000-12-05

# All Time Favorites Online Privacy Policy

**All Time Favorites Online Privacy Policy**

The All Time Favorites (ATF) system is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.

**Basic Confidentiality Policy**  
  
It is ATF policy that **personal information** , such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is **private and confidential**. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible _only_ by designated staff, and is used _only_ for the purposes for which you provide the information. _If_ you also indicate on our sites that _you would like to receive information about other ATF programs and services_ , such as publications, networking groups, or memberships, your personal information will be added to appropriate ATF mailing lists. You can indicate your desire when completing a information forms or when you send us e-mail. If at any time you change your mind and would like to add or remove your name from the ATF's mailing list, or correct your personal information, please email us at [MailList@alltimefavorites.com](mailto:MailList@alltimefavorites.com)

**No Release of Information to Third Parties**  
  
Personal information **will not be released to third parties** _except_ to further the purpose for which you provide the information, such as requesting information from vendors or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. _There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties._

**No Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information**  
  
Our computer is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our sites. This information is used only for internal purposes by ATF technical support staff.

Our computer also recognizes what sites you click on during your visit to our website. We cannot identify the visitor or the visitor's address. Site information is used to improve our website and may be used to advise vendors and potential vendors of the numbers of visitors who come to our site from their sites. No personal information is collected.

In addition, our web sites track information about the visits to our web sites. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

Click your browser's "back" button to go back to the prior page.

Thank you.

Further comments on the above policy or ways to improve it can be directed to [privacypolicy@alltimefavorites.com](mailto:privacypolicy@alltimefavorites.com)
